Naruth Kongurai

Web & Mobile Developer & Marketing Technology

1128 NE 41^{st.} Cedar E302-B, Seattle, WA 98105

+1 (206) 201-9256 | contact@naruthk.com | 🗥 www.naruthk.com | 🛅 naruthkongurai | 🕑 naruthk

Summary

Current undergraduate Research Assistant in the University of Washington's Community Data Science Collective research group. Specializes in web (front-end) and mobile application development. Super nerd who loves using the command-line-interface to develop web and mobile projects. Interested in learning new technologies if the need arises, and devising a better problem-solving method for challenging and serious tasks. Competitive in nature. Loves contributing to open-source projects.

Skills

Programming Languages: Java, Python, Swift, HTML, Javascript, PHP

Operating Systems: Windows and Mac OS

Tools: Gulp, jQuery, Bootstrap, NodeJS, React, LESS, Git Software: Adobe Photoshop, Android Studio, Xcode, Eclipse, VS Code

Work Experience

Ogilvy One Worldwide

Bangkok, Thailand

01/2017 - 09/2017

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER INTERN

- Reduced webpage sizes and increased page load speed for Thailand's NIVEA, SHOW DC Shopping Mall, and Milo websites
- Discussed UX/UI design changes with clients and Product Lead, and turned Photoshop templates to full-scale websites
- Developed API (PHP and Javascript) for fetching more than 1000+ NIVEA's customers survey reports
- Redesigned and implemented HTML email templates (Foundation-based) for Samsung Asia

Bitsee (Start-up Company)

Seattle, WA USA

ANDROID APPLICATION DEVELOPER INTERN

01/2017 - 03/2017

- Designed and built a Tutorial Section, including an interactive tutorial walkthrough that makes the app easier to navigate
- Created the company's official website (HTML5 Boilerplate, Bootstrap and jQuery), featuring an interactive app showcase design.
- Conducted unit testing on Android Studio and managed the pre-release test (beta) involving more than 100+ volunteered users

CP All Plc.

Bangkok, Thailand

07/2016 - 09/2016

ANDROID APPLICATION DEVELOPER INTERN

- Single-handedly built a rating application deployed and used internally by 7-Eleven convenience stores (9000+ stores) in 2 months.
- Created a back-end server using PHP and MySQL to store incoming data (survey results) uploaded by the mobile application
- Built a front-end website to retrieve the rating results and display them to registered users

Projects

Daily Notes - Distraction-Free (iOS Application)

App Store | 10/2017

• Developed a distraction-free note-taking app (plain text format). Available on the App Store for the iPhone and iPad.

Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineer (IEEE) Club Website

students.washington.edu/hknieee | 10/2017

- Customized an existing Wordpress theme to fit the organization's desired design.
- Served the club as one of two webmasters (the other person does more of the front-end stack)

Python Command-Line-Interface for Fetching Soccer Scores

github.com/naruthk | 08/2017

· Connected with external APIs to perform the functions of retrieving fixtures, table standings, and players information

Education